Domain Expansion.
Chimera Shadow Garden.
Esoteric Technique.
Hollow Wicker Basket.
[NARRATOR] Hollow Wicker Basket
is the origin
of New Shadow Style's
"Simple Domain."
It possesses the ability
to neutralize a domain
and counter
its guaranteed-hit factor.
This won't end well for you.
-[thuds]
-[gasps]
[NARRATOR]
The "Domain Amplification"
used by Jogo and Hanami
in Shibuya
used a domain
capable of guaranteed-hit,
guaranteed-kill technique.
[groans]
[REGGIE]
How was he able to hit me?
[NARRATOR] But they
intentionally left a space
in their cursed techniques
so that Gojo's cursed technique
could flow into it,
neutralizing his Limitless.
However, Hollow Wicker Basket
and Simple Domain aren't capable
of neutralizing
the cursed technique.
So instead, they work
by neutralizing the barrier
that's imbued
with cursed technique.
In this way,
the imbued technique's
guaranteed-hit effect
is nullified.
[groans]
[NARRATOR] But Fushiguro's
domain is incomplete.
Guess that wiped
the sneer off your face.
You damn brat!
[spits]
[NARRATOR]
When he transposed his domain
onto the space of the gymnasium,
an unexpected consequence
happened.
It forced his domain to close.
It is not imbued
with a guaranteed-hit technique.
[grunts]
You're acting
like you've already won!
[groans]
[REGGIE] Now I get it.
[NARRATOR]
Chimera Shadow Garden.
It is currently extending
Fushiguro's Ten Shadows
Technique,
and as it does so,
draws out 120%
of his latent potential.
Unfortunately for Reggie Star,
that very imperfection
is what caught him off-guard.
[REGGIE] Both his clothes
and his shikigami
had physical forms
before striking me.
That means this barrier
isn't imbued
with a guaranteed-hit technique.
The domain's buff
to his technique's abilities
is no joke, though.
This is even worse to deal with
than a simple
guaranteed-hit domain.
If he pulls
that elephant out here
and drenches me in water,
it'll take away
half of my options
and I'll probably lose.
[groans]
[Megumi grunts]
[REGGIE] But, you know,
it's so like me
to make sure
that won't happen.
-[MEGUMI] Nue!
-[Nue screeches]
[Reggie grunts]
Too slow.
I have it figured out.
Yes, I knew it.
I've had to reinforce my footing
with cursed energy
to avoid getting sucked in.
[footsteps splashing]
Because the whole bottom
of this domain
is your shadow, right?
You're able to remove
and store objects and yourself.
That's pretty convenient.
But one thing
kept nagging at me.
"Why doesn't this guy have
more weapons he can use?"
You just use that one paltry
cursed tool over and over.
Maybe it's a low-capacity tool
and you're trying to reserve
as much space for yourself,
just in case you need it
for something later on.
Either that,
or you're being forced to bear
the weight of the objects
that are stored in your shadow.
[struggling]
[REGGIE] Sounds like
the latter was spot-on.
Now I've turned the design
of your domain against you.
With three passenger cars,
your current weight
is approximately 2.4 tons.
Looks like your clones
weren't able to tolerate it.
And I bet you can't even
produce your shikigami now.
Either way, I'll just need
to keep minding
my footing around you,
as I keep adding weight
until you're crushed under it.
[MEGUMI]
Are you stupid or something?
Even if it's incomplete,
a domain is still a domain!
My shadow is everywhere!
[trumpets]
[groans]
Which one of us
will get crushed first?
-Huh, Reggie?!
-[Reggie grunts]
[♪ opening theme song playing]
[whooshing]
[NARRATOR] It is said
that a typical human
will lose consciousness
at five to six Gs.
2.4 tons.
Because Fushiguro
weighed only 60 kilograms,
that meant he was
currently suffering
the equivalent of 40 Gs.
In order to prevent his blood
from pooling in his legs
from the high Gs,
and depriving his brain
of blood flow,
Fushiguro was lowering
his posture,
and reinforcing his body
with cursed energy,
paying special attention
to his legs.
A mature African elephant
weighs three to six tons.
With the domain's improvement
to his technique's accuracy,
Max Elephant accurately
recreated its real weight.
Under that weight,
Reggie Star's right fibula
and heel bone were cracking.
[Reggie groans]
[NARRATOR] Both of them
were now under enormous strain,
and faced the possibility
of being crushed to death
at any second.
[both struggling]
[REGGIE] I screwed up.
I could've won if I had kept
the trucks in reserve.
What do I do?
I got splashed with some water
at the same time,
but my trump card's
still safe.
I could slip into his shadow
and recreate my trump card
inside it.
That would crush him for sure.
No, he's not dismissing
his domain.
But when he does decide
to dismiss it,
that means
anything still in his shadow
is going to be stuck
inside there.
What if I'm stuck
in his shadow forever?
I'll be there
even after he dies!
What's it like
inside his shadow, anyway?
It looks like a liquid,
but what if I can't
breathe in it?
Can I float?
Keep fighting!
Submerging into his shadow
is too risky.
Ah, I'm out of time.
So while stuck in this state,
I have to pull out my trump card
and activate it!
[grunts]
[gasps]
Contractual Re-Creation!
[Megumi struggling]
[straining]
[REGGIE]
I didn't make it in time.
And now I know there's no oxygen
inside of his shadow.
No buoyancy
or resistance, either.
I'm just...
sinking.
My consciousness...
is fading.
[Megumi groans] Not yet.
Keep enduring it.
Gotta wait until
I'm sure he's dead
before dismissing the domain!
Then I can expel
whatever's in my shadow.
[straining]
[gasps, coughs]
[coughing]
[REGGIE] The things I recreate,
they disappear
soon after carrying out
whatever command
I gave them to carry out.
However, I didn't give
those cars I sank any commands.
After all, I didn't want them
disappearing on me.
That means I could still issue
them a command if I want.
Something like
"Take me and rise up."
The weight
of one car is gone now,
but it was totally worth it
to save my life.
[Megumi straining]
[REGGIE] Tell you what!
I am man enough to admit it!
You are strong.
But not as strong as me!
Contractual Re-Creation!
[♪ tense music playing]
A 132-square-foot, two-story
wooden frame structure!
The framework alone weighs
at least 30 tons!
And I'm commanding it
to crush you!
[screams]
[Megumi straining]
[music ends]
[Reggie gasps] What happened?
Did I fall back
into his shadow again?
No! I'm in actual water.
How?
It's heavy.
What's the brat trying to do,
strangle me?
What power!
No. That's wrong.
This is from the weight
of those two cars that I added.
This is bad.
This time, I'm really sinking!
I have to dismiss
Contractual Re-Creation!
[gasps]
[panting]
All right.
The community gymnasium.
And in the gym's basement
is a heated swimming pool.
Did he go hiding in a shadow
and dismiss his domain?
That could ' ve forced me
to destroy the floor
and plunge into the pool.
[grunts]
[MEGUMI]
You can't use your receipts
when they're that wet, can you?
[REGGIE] He waited instead of
pursuing me right away.
Does that mean his technique
still needs to recover
after his domain exhausted it?
That's what you think?
Are you sure?
I'm sure that you can't
produce your shikigami
in your current condition.
[MEGUMI] Yeah, that's true.
So you do understand
what comes next, don't ya?
[REGGIE] He's going to use
a shikigami, just not that dog.
But none of his other ones
can deal a decisive blow.
Fine. Use it!
The moment
that you let up on me,
I'll finish you
with a counterattack!
[both grunting]
You thought Demon Dog
was some weak shikigami?
You were wrong.
What did I tell you before?
We sorcerers are all liars.
-[groans]
-[thuds]
[♪ tranquil music playing,
Camille Saint-Saëns "Le Cygne"]
[REGGIE] The domain.
The pool.
All to convince me
you couldn't use
that dog anymore.
You didn't escape
into this gymnasium.
You lured me into it.
To think I'd let
a modern sorcerer,
and a brat at that,
get the better of me.
Nue can't fly that far
carrying me,
so I couldn't escape.
I've had trouble
with that before.
Tell me,
how are you connected
to Tengen?
Who are you talking about?
Oh, right, Tengen.
That hermit
would still be alive.
Must be history's
greatest shut-in.
Okay. That's enough.
Reggie said Tengen's claims
about the Culling Game
were a bluff.
I'd be smart
to consider the possibility
Tengen and Kenjaku
are secretly connected,
and that they're both lying
about their endgames.
But that doesn't seem likely
from Reggie's reaction.
Kogane,
transfer all my points over
to this little brat.
[KOGANE] Okay.
Congratulations,
you have been granted 41 points
by Reggie Star.
And in return?
Must you assume
I have some evil plot?
I want to do at least
one good deed before I die.
By the way,
I'm just a spectator here.
Kenjaku and I weren't
ever close friends.
But I do like this game.
It certainly
makes things interesting.
That's my intuition anyway.
Now do me a favor.
After all, you did kill me.
The favor is,
let fate toy with you
before you die like a fool.
♪
[KOGANE] You have gained
five points for a kill.
[whooshing]
[sips, grunts]
I got him!
Nope! 'Cause you
dropped your guard!
You think you're Mr. Tough Guy?
What the hell!
Ugh! Why is your whole body
covered in lotion?
It might actually be sauce.
Just die!
[groans]
I pray it's only sauce!
Seriously, what's with this guy?
I've blown him up a lot!
I feel like I've killed him
at least five times.
So how come he has
so little damage?
What's wrong with sauce?
[IORI] Even his giant
head wound has healed up.
But he hasn't shown any signs
of using
reverse cursed techniques
like I do.
I don't get
what's going on with him.
Player Hazenoki.
What'd you want?
I regret to inform you
that player Reggie Star
has just died.
Huh?
[exclaims] Where you goin'?
[IORI] I'm goin' home.
I'm sick of this.
[TAKABA] Oh. Well, take a bath!
And brush your teeth!
[gasps]
Hey! How about
giving me your points?
Don't follow me.
Oh, come on!
Just think of it
as paying it forward.
Just die.
[NARRATOR] Takaba's
cursed technique, Comedian,
takes whatever he's convinced
would be funny,
and turns it into a reality.
Even Satoru Gojo is incapable
of opposing this technique.
Yet Takaba is utterly clueless
as to how his technique works.
[Remi panting]
[REMI]
I don't get it, I don't get it!
Ever since I became an adult,
I hardly understand anything.
[panting]
I've heard that all men
are actually wolves.
But it's always those wolves
who take care of
the confusing stuff for me.
It's a win-win situation.
The wolves love being in charge,
and I love not thinking
about anything.
Men always want to do stuff
for me because I'm so cute.
[panting]
The wolves
will always, always--
-[snarls]
-[gasps]
[TSUMIKI] Megumi, don't.
[REMI] You're not killing me?
[footsteps receding]
[MEGUMI] Damn it, sis.
[thuds]
Shut up already.
[♪ ethereal music playing]
[NARRATOR] Events progressed
quickly in the Sendai Colony,
far outstripping those of Tokyo.
They also started
to become increasingly fierce.
Dhruv Lakdawalla.
Current points, 91.
This is his second incarnation.
He's an old man
who single-handedly
conquered this archipelago
during the Civil War of Wa.
He possesses
two autonomous shikigami,
and the orbit of those shikigami
determines his domain.
Ryu Ishigori.
Current points, 77.
He has the greatest
cursed energy firepower
among any other remaining
player in the game.
Takako Uro.
Current points, 70.
She was originally the captain
of the Sun, Moon,
and Stars Squad.
Assassins for the Fujiwara Clan.
Her technique can
manipulate the sky.
Kurourushi.
Current points, 54.
A cockroach cursed spirit
that Kenjaku freed
from the control
of cursed spirit manipulation.
It ranks as a previously
registered special-grade.
It's currently lying dormant
until certain conditions
are met.
There was no alliance
between them,
but their complex compatibility
and opposing strength
led them into
a four-way stalemate.
But one of those pillars...
[slashes]
...has fallen.
Yuta Okkotsu.
Current points, 35.
Three months
after the Night Parade
of a Hundred Demons,
he blossomed
as a special-grade sorcerer.
He is a modern sorcerer,
rivaling the abilities
of even...
Satoru Gojo.
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[YUTA] I'll obtain
400 points on my own.
[RIKA] Which would
you like, Yuta?
[KOGANE]
It's called Kurourushi!
-[YUTA] I'll take it all!
-[RIKA] Give me back Yuta!
[YUTA] I refuse to let you
kill your best friend twice.